We are in from here.
Yes.
Please do so.
This is the live feed you have all been waiting for.
Yes, it's on.
I couldn't sleep last night. I was too excited.
When I thought about the live delivery.
I couldn't sleep because I was so nervous.
Nervous?
I was nervous.
I'm so nervous.
Oh my god, my heart is racing.
My pulse isn't normal. It's irregular.
I'll just put a normal pulse.
I'm a little nervous about normal irregular pulse.
What's this thing called "fluid tachycardia"?
There is such a thing as a healthy irregular pulse.
Is there such a thing as a healthy irregular pulse?
A natural one.
Is that so?
It's like the heart bar is shaped a little funny.
It's a feeling.
Feelings?
Normal, like this, thump, thump.
Thank you!Hi!
Hi!
Is everyone's heart okay?
Are you okay?
What's the topic?
I'll get to that.
Well, well, well.
This week's shift is in Balikata.
It's crunch time.
Whoo!
I just made a really loud voice.
Surprise. I was surprised myself.
It felt like a sharp sound in my eardrums.
It's scary.
I wonder how loud I can make my voice.
I'm sure it's quite loud.
I've never tried it.
You know how many decibels I often hear at construction sites?
I might go in front of a construction site and try to make my voice a little bit louder.
I wonder how much it would go up.
Hurrah!
I'd like you to try it.
I'd love to see you do it.By all means.
Well, well, well, well.
How is it? It's still a little hot.
Yes, it's still hot.
It's still hot.
How did it go this year? Did you have a good year?
The heat? No, I'm not okay.
Not okay?
It wasn't okay.
It wasn't.
It wasn't?
No, it wasn't.
So it's usually air-conditioned or something, like the company you're listening to,
Or indoors?
Well, I could appreciate it now. Air conditioners.
No, it's true.
There were many times during the day when I thought, "This is not good.
That's right.
Bathing in the air conditioner.
Is it OK in the summer?
Surprisingly, there were quite a lot of summer gigs, so I didn't have to do it too much because I was moving around.
That's good.
I think it's good to sweat and rehydrate.
That might be important.
Take a good shower.Take a good bath.
Well, that being said, though, isn't it already getting pretty cool at night?
Yes, it is.
A little bit lately.
But, you know.
But it's okay at night.
Maybe you hear some insects or something.
That's right.
It's already coming from somewhere.
It's about time, please.
Please do.
Okay, I'll do it.
You're doing the "shwah, shwah, shwah, shwah, shwah, shwah, shwah, shwah, shwah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, for now, let's move on with the main part of the program,
I would like to hear your valuable opinions later on.
So, let's get started, shall we?
Let's begin, shall we?
OK, so...
Well...
Friday!
Friday.
Yes!
Yes!Yes!
Well, a week goes by so fast!
Yes, it does.
But you know what, I've been back to Barigato again this week, and I've done it several times.
It's interesting to discover new things, isn't it, this guy?
Yes, he's right.
He's got a lot of material.
He has a lot of material, so he has a lot of drawers.
It's interesting that he's not good at rubbing his face.
I don't think he understands this, but...
But it's interesting to watch from the other side.
I see.
You know, it's like... how do you say...
For example, soba noodles.
I thought it was supposed to be "sil-sil-sil".
That's right.
Only Barigato doesn't make any sound.
It's like a surprise human, isn't it?
And that's why everyone says it's so cute.
That's right.
I think it's going to be on the air somewhere this week.
Please look forward to it.
Silently.
Mr. Barigato is silently eating something in silence.Mr. Barigato silently and silently eats something
Little by little, it's being swallowed up like this.
I can't help but look at it.
Like an aha experience
I wonder what's changing.
Yes, well, first of all...
Today
On the small reading, it's already September.
Yes, sir.
On the small reading, it's September.
So, first of all, let's do the "what day is it tomorrow" thing.
First of all, let's see what day it is tomorrow.
Today is the 14th of September?
Fifteen. - Fifteen.
15, tomorrow is the 16th.
September is already half over.
Oh no!
It's past half time.
After half time, it's time to drink water, like in soccer.
There's drinking time too!
It's a vacation!
One break, one water break.
It's kind of a joke, isn't it?
Maybe we should change the name.
So, let's see...Let's see, so let's see...
Wait a minute, please.
Let's see...
Tomorrow is September 16th, the day of high definition.
It's 9 by 9, 16 by 16, 9 by 16, and in the old days, it was 3 by 4.
It used to be 3 to 4, and 3 to 4 to 3, don't you know? What are you talking about?
What? Wait a minute, you don't know that? Are you kidding me? Are you kidding me? What are you talking about?
What the hell is this?
Alive?
But it's kind of brown?
Brownish, yes, like that.
What about that?
That's another 4-3, for sure.
Oh, really?
Yes, that's right.
I don't get that feeling.
I don't know, I just don't feel it.
Well, that's true, isn't it?
Wait a minute, by the way, the high-definition is...
Let's see, it's 9 to 16, so September 16th.
Oh, I see.
And there are two high definition days, the other one is November 25th.
The other is November 25th, because the number of operating lines is 1125 for HDTV.
November 25th.
And the other one is November 25th, which is the number of operating lines, 1125 for HDTV and 525 for HDTV.That four-to-three before, there were only 525 lines.
I mean, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
Oh, you guys can't see it at all.
I don't know how to say it... I don't know how to say it...
It's like the resolution of a camera. In the past, the number of lines was much smaller. Now, however, there are 1,125 lines.
But now there are 1,125 of them. Like the Dancing Maneuvers. Is that so? What do you mean?
Enough, enough, enough. What did you just say?
Wait a minute. It doesn't matter. Wait a minute. So it's been 16-9 ever since you had the heart of a thing?
Yes, I think so, 4 to 3. I think it was 4 to 3 in 2000, I think it was 2000.
I think it was 4:3, I think it was 4:3, I think it was 4:3 in 2000, 2000.
So in 2002, there was the Japan-Korea World Cup soccer tournament. That is why HDTV became popular all at once.
So it may have been around for a while, but it probably started in the first half of the year 2000. Before that, it was 4 vs. 3. Before that, it was 4 to 3.
Then I don't know. I was born in 2007. What do you mean, born in 2007? Don't be silly, it's a little late for that.
I was born in 1999. I was born in 1999. Oh, right, just barely. I've been 16-9 since I can remember. That's right.
Oh, my God, you guys, 4-3, there are people on TV who don't know what 4-3 is. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. 4 vs. 3. Don't take me for a fool. Don't take it easy on me, Blanca. On TV, it's 9 to 16, right?
So, in the beginning, the width of the screen increased. So, first of all, the resolution was improved so much that the screen became very beautiful. I was surprised.
I bought my first TV around the time of the 2002 World Cup.
I bought one in 2002, just before the World Cup.
It's a 12 to 9 screen. When I bought it, I could see the grass like this, and when there was a corner kick, I would say, "Oh, wow!
But when it was 4 vs. 3, it was green and kind of mellow, you know.
But even so, I was totally surprised at first, like, "Oh, I see, I see.
So now that the width is wider, you know, dramas and movies are wider to begin with.
It's the same with TV dramas and historical dramas, but up until now, it's all about the black here.
Even now, in old movies, the right and left sides are blacked out.
So, for example, if I say, "Let's take a balicata shot like this," the right and left sides of the image are blacked out.So, for example, if I say, "Let's take a balicata shot like this," and I take a 4:3 shot, it should look like this, right?
So, for example, if I say, "Let's take a balicata shot like this," and you take a 4:3 shot like this, it would look like this.
And also, the resolution has gone up too much, so that period drama aspect has gone up too much.
But with high-definition, suddenly the torture of the three torturers looks like a mask.
The wig wearers were thinking, "This is a bad idea," and now they're trying to make it so you can't tell.
That's how big a revolution it was in the TV industry.
I mean, this was the biggest shock to me since I made my debut in the theater.
I thought 4 to 3 was a little bit old fashioned, so the TV in the back is 4 to 3....... Yes, yes, 4 to 3.......
I see... that's why it's 4 to 3 now.
Some mv's are intentionally made 4 to 3 to make it look old-fashioned.
I'm not sure how much fun this is going to be, but it was mainly me who was having fun.
I see... is it going to be wider?
What's that 16 to 9 is like 32 to 10 or something... I wonder how close it is... so now... it's natural to say 4K on TV, isn't it?
Yes, but 8K, which has the highest resolution, is the most popular.
We don't usually use 8K.
But if we had cameras and equipment that could shoot 8K, we would be able to shoot even better than this.
If we had a camera or equipment that could take 8K images, we would be able to see the wig even more clearly than this.
You can even see the letters clearly.
If you're looking at it with the naked eye, you can see the letters clearly.
We call this 3K. 3K.
It's dirty and disgusting.
We were called "3K dirty and disgusting" and "stinky" and "smelly.
That's what it means. I don't know what "3K" means.
I don't know what "4K" means, but I work in the restaurant industry.
Mr. Keebo, Yokosuka City, Male, Occupation Ebichu FamilyMr. Keebo, male, Yokosuka, Japan Occupation Ebichu Family
Hey, this is Service Chat.
I'm sure you're right, that's great, too.
Oh, oh, oh!
I've been reading your blog every day and I've been thinking about you a lot.
I've been wondering about something for a while... the part in the opening of the show where you show the video of the opening of the show... could it be the video that was shot on the day of your debut in Odate?
I can't help but think so, since your hair and the clothes you're wearing are the same as the day you made your debut in Odate.
I'm sure it's been a long time, but yes, now that I've seen it, I can't help but wonder if I know too much about this truth.
Maybe I know too much... but I'm scared...
I'm not afraid, but we should form some kind of internal investigation committee.
If it's just us, it'll just be the content. You're right. They won't believe us.
Internal investigation? Sure. I mean...
I didn't kill the tree in front of the company.
It's serious. It's serious.
Well, maybe... that's why I'm asking...
I don't know... it was a busy day for my debut in Odate... I didn't have time to take pictures like that.
I took it on the day.
Thank you very much. It was a very special construction project.
We had to keep up with the rhythm of this one, this one, this one, this one, this one.
Like this, like this, like this...
Well, well, well, well...
I'm relying on you to say...
Well...
This one's good, too. I think he's a college student.
Desmotiros, Hachioji City, Tokyo. Thank you.Desmos Churros, Hachioji City, Tokyo, Japan Thank you.
The oldest in Yamanashi Prefecture, with my circle of friends.
Is it called "s-sup," "sup," "sap," "sap," "sap," "sap," "sap," "sap.
That's right... "sup" is this... "sup" is that... "sup" is that...
Not "booboo sap"!
It's not "boo boo sap.
It was so nice to go on the lake in the wilderness.
This one too, this one, this one, all of them, this one too, this one too, this one too, this one too, this one too, this one too, this one too.
In the morning, there is a guy standing on a surfboard and doing this with oars, that's it.
They go to the lake or something like this now.
I wonder if they get excited at night and go to the farmer's market.
Fireworks and stuff... and barbecues near the lake.
Barbecue...
I'm so envious of your youth.
I'll do a Bob Sapp impersonation.
And... this is just another picture.
8... but it's the same short one...
I've got some pictures from Sarpong... which one is this?
I'm sure it's easy to see even if I write it down.
Thank you very much.
This is a burger... at Yakushi Pond in Machida.
Yakushi Pond in Machida... a big park there... a cafe there...
What is Machida, a hamburger paradise?
I think it's called "Shogun Burger".Yes, it's called Shogun Burger, isn't it?
I said "family", but the contents of the burger were not that great, because they ignored the filling.
I don't know what it's called, but it's a gorgeous name, but it's really delicious!
It's got bacon, cheese, honey mustard, honey mustard, fried egg, sweet and spicy.
The burger is a big burger, but it's not on a piece of paper.
The big burger is put in the paper, right?
I don't think it's right to cut the burger, but...
We don't mind, but it's not so easy with girls... who don't open their mouths and cover it with paper.
Who's the one hiding it?
who's hiding this?If it's not like that, why don't you just eat it?
You don't have room for paper paper paper paper.
boo boo!
Oh, and there's dessert... and this... and this... and this... and this... and this... and this... and this...
Oh, this is the French toast... if you don't talk about icons...
You look like you're going to eat it. I eat French toast maybe once every three years.
I've had it about once every 4 years... and I think it was once during the Olympics, around the time of the Beijing Olympics.
It's like the Olympics, like the Olympics.
It's an ice cream with custard, but it looks like it's going to be good.
This is Zero One Cafe, which I introduced to you before.
If you go to Yakushi Pond, please try this burger and this... this is the same restaurant, so I hope you'll try it!
I hope you'll try it!
You've got a good appetite.
Fireworks are the best part of summer. So we had fireworks.
I had fireworks with my mother and father. You only talk about four people.I did fireworks with that mother and father. Your story only has about four people in it.
Hon! My mother, my father, and Shingo... four characters.
I can't help it, I don't have any friends. Weak! I can't help it. Make it up!
He really doesn't seem to have any. He really doesn't have any.
I really don't have any.
He said he's a bariker... and not a member of Ebichu... but a friend.
I'm sure you have friends in your hometown... but I shouldn't have asked you this...
I've been in high school for four months, and I still can't make friends... is it okay if I don't make friends right away?
I've been in high school for four months, but I still don't have any friends.What's with this bad aftertaste? It doesn't make me feel any better.
Well, well, well, well... Did you enjoy the fireworks?
I haven't done it much myself. I was thinking of doing it when I go somewhere.
I thought I'd like to do it when I go somewhere, but I figured you probably won't come, so I went with my mom and dad.
Why are your mom and dad so conveniently close to you? Well, we live together.
But sometimes it's hard to arrange a fireworks party with friends.
They have their own jobs, too. They're around at night.
No, no, no... Yes, they do.
I don't get it. A lot of things don't add up.
A lot of things don't add up in the Nakajima family.
There's no such thing as a mystery.
Well, well, well, well. Let's have a look at this corner, shall we?
What a creature!
A shopping expert, Monopoly, gave it to us.
Thank you very much. Oh, wait a minute...
I'm sorry, Mr. Monopoly, but I'm afraid we'll have to cancel your order next week.I'm sorry, Mr. Monopoly, but I'll be with you next week.
I'm sorry, I'm with you, I made a mistake, I'm sorry, I'm with you next week, I'm sorry, I'm with you next week, I'm with you next week.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm with you, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm going in to search for Mouri...
I'm getting a devil's charge for the hamburgers.
What hamburger money? He looks like he wants to eat.
I'm sorry, please squeeze it.
Mr. Naotong is silently paying for the Devil's Charge.
Devil's Charge. Thank you.
Oh, this ain't it.
Oh, it's a quitter.
We've got a creature from the bag in Hachioji City, Tokyo!Wait a minute... everything here has been collected...
First of all, thank you very much!
There's an anime called Golden Kamui... about a creature that appears in it... the "Ainugo
Ainugo.
It's okay if you don't make friends.
We'll do our best.
We're here for you.
What's wrong?
Even if you don't have friends...
We're here for you.
That's a good thing, isn't it? - No, I don't have any friends either.
I don't have any friends either.
Well... nothing in particular.Uh, nothing in particular.
Nothing in particular.
It's slow, it's slow, it's slow, people are reacting...
What are you doing?
What are you training for?
Yes, so what a surprise about the other guy...
Kotankorokamui.
Kotankoro Kamui.
You didn't mention Golden Kamui.
It's interesting.
Really?
I can't believe it.
We're just now...Yeah, I'm on break right now.
I'm on a break, so I'm watching a Netflix cartoon.
It's so funny!
I can't help but watch it all the time.
I see.
It's a very deep story.
Kotankoro kamui.
What's a kamui?
Kamui what?
Kotankoro kamui.
Heh.Heh.
By the way, this creature is basically only found in Hokkaido.
Oh!
In Japan.
You mean it's real? You mean it exists in real life?
Yes, they exist in real life.
Did you think they were some kind of imaginary creature?
You're talking about anime.
But cartoons are realistic, so is the merge screen.
I don't know.
They exist in real life.
I've never seen it, but...
I've never seen it.I wonder what it is.
By the way, I'll give you a hint... it's a national monument.
A national? Japan? Japan.
A natural monument... Oh!
Oh, here it comes!
It's called Tenki, isn't it?
But whether I can write is another story.
It's true that my drawing ability is a little low.
I don't know what it is anymore...
Kotankorokorokamui
Okay, so you think you can go to Barigato?
Then, Kotankorokorokamui...Okay, small coal kolo-kolo-kamui.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
What's this?
It looks like a Buddha statue.
Yes, it does.
Yes.
This is from the person himself.
First of all, a comment.
I've created a creature of fantasy.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's called a "kokan korokamui".
I think it's like a kokoro korokamui.
I see...The Little Coal Korokamui.
Yes.
Like this.
I think this is where it rolls.
Yes, it rolls.
And this area also rolls around.
When I first drew this far
I knew it didn't exist in reality.
But it's impossible, isn't it?But you can't, can you?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's too late to tell me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll say it when you say it. I'll say it now.
I'll tell you now.
Are they real or not?
I'll tell you when you tell me.
I'll tell you if it's real or not.
I'll get angry.
I'm angry.
I heard you say "kokan kolokamui".
I thought it sounded like gold.
Oh, I see.It's a star.
Yes, sir.
And...
This stick figure...
I'm burnt out.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Burned out
I'm burnt out.
That's good
So I'm like, "Oh, no, I'm not going to do this anymore.So from this kind of thing, it's like, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's right.
He said it's too late.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well then, Sensei, please...
Oh!
Are you a fan?
No, no...
What is it?
I don't know.
Well, I'm not criticizing you.
I'm not criticizing you, but...
I understand.
Maybe this is...
If I were to write it, for example...
I think I could write it in about 3.8 seconds.
But it's taking so long.What's taking so long?
The eyes.
Oh, there.
I had to make the run-on lines a little longer.
I don't run my mouth long.
I don't lengthen my run-on-mouth.
That's why it took so long.
Yes, it did.That's right.
I see.
That swan?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
The swan.
By swan, do you mean the swan?
Yes, the swan.
I've never seen a swan.
No, I haven't.
Actually...
Not really.
I've only heard of the Swan.
That's what happens when you write from your imagination.
I see...
That's right.
It's amazing to see them up close.
You're good at that.
I see.In my imagination, it's like this.
In my head, it's a swan.
Swans are amazing.
I don't know what it is.
There's a revolution happening right now.
Thank you very much.
Kotankorokamui...Yes, that's right, Kotankorokamui, what a surprise!
It's called "Shimabukuro", isn't it?
I was about to write the first thing.
It's like a god who protects the village.
Kamui means "god.
He's a god.
Kotan is a village...
Yes, yes, yes.
I think "kotan" means "village.
This is Japan's largest sack.
It's about 180 cm long when its wings are spread.
The width is...
That's me!
That's okay, it's not that surprising.
Isn't it huge?
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes!
And they say it's a natural treasure.
I should've written it down.I heard that this one is in an amazing zoo or something.
I heard it's in a zoo in Hokkaido.
It seems to be a very valuable bag.
How frustrating!
Striped Owl
I was going to write about the bag at first, butI was going to write the bag first.
Well, well, well, well, that's about it.
So if you say it's a little bit beak-like
It's more or less like...
Butterflies.
It's a little stuck.
That's right.
Yes, it is.
What's this?
There's no way to describe it.
Yes, it is.
It's so far removed from the rest of the world that it's almost impossible to imagine.
It's like...
Yes, yes, yes.
So, I think it's time to end the live broadcast.
I'd like to talk to you all about something from the value model.
Are you getting any color?
Are they here?
Yes, I'm here.Thank you very much.
It's great.
Colors are here.
One after another.
Wow.Wow.
That's great. That's great.
Everyone's watching it. It's so interesting.
You should definitely see it. It's amazing... the relationship between nature and humans.
And human desires... it's so interesting... it's not a production... but it's like a true story.
Let's take a look.
There's a little girl, Ashikaga Hane, who's cute.
It's a good movie.
I see... I guess I'll just have to write it down.
I'm sure you're right.
The more I look at it, the more I wonder what kind of creature it is.
Well, well, well, well... I'll see you next week at 8:00 p.m. for the live broadcast.
I'll see you next week at 8:00 p.m.
Finally, do that thing, BNS.
I'm back now.
I'll catch up with you next week.
Thank you very much.